

# JOMAR CLADO

FRONT - END DEVELOPER

## CONTACT

- **1** +639319918329
- cladojomar881@gmail.com
- 2 182, Catalotoan, San Jose, Camarines Sur
- https://github.com/jomar567
- in www.linkedin.com/in/jomarclado

# **SKILLS**

- HTML (3 years)
- CSS (3 years)
- Bootstrap (3 years)
- SCSS/SASS (3 years)
- Javascript (2 years)
- React (lyear)
- Responsive Design (3 years)
- Github (3 years)
- Figma (Knowledgeable)
- PHP (Knowledgeable)
- Laravel (Knowledgeable)
- MySQL(Knowledgeable)

## REFERENCE

Available upon request

## **PROFILE**

I am an experienced front-end developer with over 3 years of experience in front-end development. Strong creative and analytical skills. Team player with an eye for detail. Can handle work pressure, fast learner and willing to learn new skills and knowledge.

# **EDUCATION**

#### **Bachelor of Science in Information Technology**

Partido State University - Goa, Camarines Sur 2015 - 2019

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **Front-end Developer**

Feemo Global Solutions Inc. l Makati 2019 - 2022

- Planned website development, converting mockups into usable web presence with HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, and VueJS coding.
- Engaged with clients to plan and optimize site issues and queries.
- Multi-tasked across multiple functions and roles to meet deadlines and organizational expectations.

Develop web applications using Javascript and ReactJS.

# PROJECT EXPERIENCE

**KODEGO BOOTCAMP**October 2022- February 2023 Full-Stack Web Development

- Develop and integrated website using HTML, CSS, ReactJS, APIs, TailwindCSS, Bootstrap, Laravel, PHP and MySQL.
- Lead a team, communicating effectively to set priorities and expectations for each task.